{
    "1": {
        "question": "Write your name using print().",
        "solution": "print(\"Your Name\")"
    },
    
    "2": {
        "question": "Write how to add 3 and 7",
        "solution": "3 + 7"
    },

    "3": {
        "question": "Write how to do floor division with 2 and 7 and assign the quotient to        the variable result",
        "solution": "result = 2 // 7"
    },

    "4": {
        "question": "Convert the string '1987' to an integer value",
        "solution": "int(\"1987\")"
    },
    
    "5": {
        "question": "Assign a value to variable idnum",
        "solution": "idnum = {integer value}"
    },
    
    "6": {
        "question": "Write how to calculate 65% of 86",
        "solution": "86 * 0.65"
    },

    "7": {
        "question": "Write code to ask for an input of what is your favorite color? and store it in the variable favcolor",
        "solution": "favcolor=input(\"What is your favorite color\")"
    },

    "8": {
        "question": "Write how to subtract 19 from 10 and store the value in the variable difference",
        "solution": "difference = 19 - 10"
    },

    "9": {
        "question": "Write how to ask for an input of what your age is and store it in the variable studentage as an integer value",
        "solution": "studentage = int(input(\"What is your age?\")"
    },

    "10": {
        "question": "Write how to display your response to the question: Are you okay?",
        "solution": "print(\"yes\")"
    }
}
